wei.xin.wy0@is.naist.jp

About Me

I am a highly motivated M2 student at CARELab, NAIST, with a strong interest in healthcare monitoring. Currently, I am focusing on developing methods to estimate visual diseases at an early stage using daily eye behaviors. My research interests include physiological signals, signal processing, and pattern recognition.

Experience _____

Cybernetics and Reality Engineering Laboratory

Nara, Japan

SPRING SEMINAR TUTOR

Feb. 2023 - Mar. 2023

- · Shimmer sensor and data analysis tutorial
- · Experimental setup

Digit Fujian Internet-of-Things Laboratory of Environmental Monitoring

RESEARCH INTERNSHIP

- · Kernel Density Estimation via LSH
- Multi-model Similarity Search
- · Recommender System and Clustering
- Real-time Anomaly Detection and Analysis System

Fuzhou, China

Sept. 2018 - Aug. 2019

Dec. 2017 - July 2018

Aug. 2017 - Dec. 2017 Mar. 2017 - Aug. 2017

Education

NARA Institute of Science and Technology

M.S. IN INFORMATION SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Nara, Japan

Oct. 2021 - Current

· Studies on methods to estimate visual diseases at an early stage from daily eye behaviors

Fujian Normal University)

Fuzhou, China

B.S. IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Sept. 2015 - June 2019

- Learned software design, software development and programming languages.
- GPA: 3.88/4.0 (2/192)

Honors & Awards

- Outstanding Undergraduate Award, Fujian Normal University
- Outstanding Undergraduate Student Paper Award, Fujian Normal University 2019

Publication

GLDH: Toward More Efficient Global Low-density Locality-Sensitive Hashing for High **Dimensions**

Information Science

Yiqi Li, Ruliang Xiao, **Xin Wei**, Huakun Liu, Shi Zhang, and Xin Du

2020

OPRCP: Approximate Nearest Neighbor Binary Search Algorithm for Hybrid Data over WMSN Blockchain

EURASIP Journal on Wireless Communications and Networking

HUAKUN LIU, XIN WEI, RULIANG XIAO, LIFEI CHEN, XIN DU, AND SHI ZHANG

2018

Skills

Programming Language

C/C++, PYTHON, JAVA, GO, SCALA, HTML/CSS/JS

Technical Software

MTEX, ARDUINO